http://www.poshusa.org/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
The Priests of the Sacred Heart are committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our website.  You may provide as much personal information as you feel comfortable with disclosing.  The Priests of the Sacred Heart do not release any personal information to another party without your permission unless required by law or court order.
This is a secure site.  Information you send to this site and information the site sends back to your computer or digital device is encrypted as it passes through the Internet.  This secure site service is offered for your protection.
No personal data is collected at the site.  After you depart the site your data is no longer retained in memory or on a hard disk.  We collect email addresses and personal information only when you volunteer it to us by way of contacting us for more information, signing up for email or postal mail programs, sending your prayer intentions or making a prayer request, donation or sacrificial offering.
Friends who make donations, place requests or otherwise provide personal information to us are added to our contact database.  This allows us to track our interactions with you so we can better meet your needs, and helps us provide you with devotional support and news about the work of the Priests of the Sacred Heart.  You may choose to cancel contact at any time by informing us by email of by calling us at (800) 448-7674.
Because our friends are a special part of our extended family, we occasionally add phone and birthdate information, available from public sources, to our contact database for purposes of thanking you and recognizing you for your support.  To be excluded from these programs, please contact us by email or call (800) 448-7674.
Receive News and Updates from the Priests of the Sacred Heart through Email.
JOIN!
×
